export const questions = [
  {
    question: 'What is the correct name of the React lifecycle method?',
    answers: ['componentWillMount', 'thisComponentWillMount', 'componentWillMountSoon', 'componentsWillMountSir'],
    correctAnswer: 'componentWillMount'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is React?',
    answers: ['A JavaScript library', 'A JavaScript framework', 'A JSX framework', 'The newest version of Angular'],
    correctAnswer: 'A JavaScript library'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Flux has been designed by...',
    answers: ['Google', 'Amazon', 'Facebook', 'Grid Dynamics'],
    correctAnswer: 'Facebook'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the correct names of the component types in React',
    answers: ['functional and unfunctional components', 'functional and class components', 'smart and beautiful components', 'app and shared components'],
    correctAnswer: 'functional and class components'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Redux used for in React?',
    answers: ['Managing global state', 'Configuring webpack', 'Configuring Eslint', 'Managing styles'],
    correctAnswer: 'Managing global state'
  },
  {
    question: 'In React the render() method is used only in...',
    answers: ['Styled components', 'Functional components', 'Smart components', 'Dumb components'],
    correctAnswer: 'Smart components'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is true about Flux Dispatcher?',
    answers: ['The dispatcher is used to broadcast payloads to registered callbacks', 'Dispatcher is used to checking changes in DOM', 'The dispatcher is used to set state in React application', 'The dispatcher is used to send data to components'],
    correctAnswer: 'The dispatcher is used to broadcast payloads to registered callbacks'
  },
  {
    question: 'PropTypes is used for...',
    answers: ['Validation', 'getPropsValue', 'getDefaultProps', 'typechecking'],
    correctAnswer: 'typechecking'
  },
  {
    question: 'What kind of application architecture is widely used together with ReactJs',
    answers: ['Flux', 'Flux with MVC', 'Flex', 'JSX architecture'],
    correctAnswer: 'Flux'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can you use ReactJs without flux?',
    answers: ['Yes, but then you will have to use MVC', 'No', 'Yes', 'No, itâ€™s in core of ReactJS'],
    correctAnswer: 'Yes, but then you will have to use MVC'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which function is invoked just before render() during component update?',
    answers: ['componentDidMount()', 'componentInit()', 'componentWillUpdate()', 'beforeRender()'],
    correctAnswer: 'componentWillUpdate()'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can you use ReactJs with AngularJs on same web application?',
    answers: ['No, because both are using virtual DOM', 'Yes', 'No, because you can have only one view layer related library per project while using webpack, babel or browserify', 'No, because ReactJs will re-render all html after initial load'],
    correctAnswer: 'Yes'
  }
]